Welcome to the future
Generation X is a tv movie, action, fantasy film directed by Jack Sholder.
A group of young mutants--humans with a genetic variation that gives them superpowers and makes
them feared by the population at large--begin training at a school for heroes.
Their studies are interrupted when they must rescue one of their
number from a mad scientist who can enter others' dreams.
Russel Tresh, played by Matt Frewer.
Emma Frost, played by Finola Hughes.
Sean Cassidy, played by Jeremy Ratchford.
Jubilation Lee / Jubilee, played by Heather McComb.
Angelo Espinosa / Skin, played by Agustin Rodriguez.
Kurt Pastorius, played by Randall Slavin.
Generation X is a television pilot directed by Jack
Sholder that aired on Fox on February 20, 1996.
It was later broadcast as a television film.
It is based on the Marvel comic book series of the same
name, a spin-off of the X-Men franchise.
It was produced by New World Entertainment and Marvel Entertainment Group.
The film explores themes of superhero, mutant, based on comic, super power.
The tone is thought_provoking.